http://www.ajilon.com/privacy-policy/

Welcome to our new website! Read about what we've changed »
x
General Privacy Policy
Last Updated: November 2019
Accounting Principals, Inc., DBA Ajilon, (“Company”, “we”, “us”, “our”) is committed to protecting and respecting your privacy.
This General Privacy Policy describes our privacy practices in relation to the information we collect from you when you visit our website, which is accessible at https://www.ajilon.com, or when you access or use any applications or features made available by us on or through or in connection with this Website or our services that link to this General Privacy Policy (collectively, the “Website”).
Note that when we collect Personal Information (defined below) from or about you in connection with a potential job opportunity, our Candidate Privacy Information Statement also applies and should be reviewed. You can read our Candidate Privacy Information Statement by visiting https://www.ajilon.com/candidate-privacy/.
Index:
Personal Information we may collect from you in using this Website
How we use your Personal Information
Do you have to give us your Personal Information?
How long do you keep my Personal Information?
Sharing with third parties
Cookies and automated technology
International users
Do we transfer or store your data outside the United States?
Data security
Your choices regarding your Personal Information
Your rights
Verifying your Identity
Shine the Light
Children’s privacy
Changes to this General Privacy Policy
Contact
Personal Information we may collect from you in using this Website
When you visit and interact with this Website, we collect information about you, including Personal Information. “Personal Information” means information that identifies or relates to you, or as defined under applicable law. The following identifies the categories of Personal Information we collect directly from you (or about you) and how we collect such data:
Online forms
and accounts: When you complete an online form or create an
account on our Website, we may collect contact information such as your
name (first and last), e-mail address, telephone number, physical address,
and online user account details (collectively, “Identifiers”). We may also
collect information pertaining to your professional qualifications,
including your educational and professional background and salary
(collectively, “Education and Qualifications”).
Communications
with us online: We will collect any Personal Information you provide
to us when you use our contact forms (for example “Contact”, “Contact us
today”, “Send us a message”, or “Contact us about working together”).
Providing us your Personal Information via our contact forms is not
required; however, please note that fields marked with an asterisk (*) are
mandatory fields, because we have determined we need this information to
comply with or respond to your request, or to improve your future
experiences with us and our Website. Other information or Personal
Information you share with us when completing our contact forms is at your
sole discretion. If you contact us, we will keep a record of that
correspondence in accordance with our established retention protocol.
Marketing: We also may
collect information for marketing purposes and analysis, including
information on how you respond to email, SMS, phone and other marketing campaigns
as well as feedback you provide about us and our services through our
satisfaction surveys (collectively, “Correspondence and Feedback”).  Messaging and data rates may apply
for any SMS, MMS, and other electronic communications (typically, this is based
on your carrier and service plan).  For more
information, please visit our Terms of Use.
Your company’s
staffing needs: If you are interested in our staffing solutions, we
may collect Personal Information and other information about you in
connection with your company’s employment needs, including without
limitation, Identifiers such as your name (first and last), e-mail
address, telephone number, as well as your company name, job title, job
function, job level, industry, staffing or employment challenges, current
recruitment model, your location, sector, experience working with our
brands, company registration number, purpose of attendance (at an event),
size of opportunity, and type of staffing need.
Social media,
online forums, blogs, message boards: We also may collect Personal Information and other
information about you when you choose to interact with us through social
media platforms on which we are active. In addition, we also may collect
the Personal Information you make available on your public social network
profiles and on other public locations, including, without limitation, on
Facebook, LinkedIn, Twitter, Instagram, or other company websites and/or
job boards. The Personal Information we collect in this manner may include
Identifiers (name (first and last), contact information, and location) and
Education and Qualifications (education, training courses and internships,
and work experience), skill sets (for example, foreign language skills),
professional or employment-related information (education and work
experience), and any other information you make available on social media
platforms and other public locations (collectively, “Social Media
Information”).
Career
opportunities: If you apply for a career opportunity with or
through us, we may collect Personal Information and other information from
you, which may include Identifiers such as your contact information (name
(first and last), physical address, telephone number, e-mail address), and
Education  and Qualifications, which
includes education, training courses and internships, and work experience,
skill sets (for example, foreign language skills) and any other
information you listed on your resume or CV. For more information about
our collection practices for job candidates, please visit our Candidate
Privacy Information Statement, available at https://www.ajilon.com/candidate-policy/.
Cookies and
automated technology: For more information about the information we
collect about your equipment browsing actions, and patterns, please
consult the “Cookies and automated technology” section below.
We also collect any other Personal Information you
choose to provide to us or we obtain about you.
Sensitive Personal Information. When you visit or interact with our Website, you are not required to submit information that may be considered sensitive, including your race or ethnic origin or data concerning your health or sexual orientation. If you decide to provide us with sensitive Personal Information, we will handle the information according to the practices identified in this General Privacy Policy as well as those identified in the Candidate Privacy Information Statement available at https://www.ajilon.com/candidate-policy/. We reserve the right to delete the information from our databases in accordance with applicable law.
Back to top
How we use your Personal Information
We collect and use the information or Personal Information we collect from or about you, including your Identifiers, Education and Qualifications, Correspondence and Feedback, and Social Media Information, for the following business purposes:
to provide you,
our clients and prospective clients, and our candidates and prospective
candidates with our services.
to best tailor
content and resources according to your preferences.
to respond to
your requests or questions when you contact us.
to help us
create, publish, and improve content most relevant to you.
to ensure that
the content provided through the Website is presented in the most
effective manner for you and for your device.
to allow you to
participate in interactive features of our Website, when you choose to do
so.
to further develop and improve the Website, and
systems to better serve you. This mainly takes place in the context of new
IT systems and processes so that information about you may be used in the
testing of those new IT systems and processes.
where necessary, to comply with any legal
obligation.
for our business contacts, to attempt to establish
or strengthen a business relationship with you. This may include, for
example, informing you how we can assist you with our services.
we also may use your information in:
investigating or responding to incidents and
complaints, and/or
complying with investigations carried out by the
police, government or regulators.
We also use the Personal Information we collect for commercial purposes. We may use your Identifiers, Education and Qualifications, Correspondence and Feedback, and Social Media Information in order:
to send you direct messaging or marketing via email,
text message, and/or other communication means. You may opt-out of
receiving future messaging or marketing communications at any time by
emailing us using the information listed in the “Contact” section below.  Messaging and data rates may apply
for any SMS, MMS, and other electronic communications (typically, this is
based on your carrier and service plan).  For more
information, please visit our Terms of Use.
to inform you about services, products, events that
might be of interest to you (we may communicate by email, telephone, text
message, mail and/or other communication methods).
to send to you other information – such as Company
upcoming events or newsletters – that may be of interest to you.
to perform analytical research on our prospective
client and candidate base, including the content, and the
services/products in which they are interested.
to transfer data to third parties (see the “Sharing
with third parties” section below).
Back to top
Do you have to give us your Personal Information?
You do not have to provide your Personal Information to us when generally navigating our Website. However, if you do not provide us with a required minimum, it may limit the services you can receive from us.
Back to top
How long do you keep my Personal Information?
We retain your Personal Information as long as necessary to fulfil the purposes set out in this General Privacy Policy in accordance with applicable legal and regulatory requirements.
Back to top
Sharing with third parties
To facilitate our efficient use of your information and Personal Information, and to provide you with content and/or resources, to fulfil a request you make of us, or to otherwise provide our services, we disclose your information, including the Personal Information identified in the “Personal Information we may collect from you in using this Website” section above, to the following third parties. :
To our
suppliers.
We engage suppliers to carry out administrative and operational work in
support of our relationship with you. The supplier(s) are subject to
contractual and other legal obligations to preserve the confidentiality of
your data and to respect your privacy, and they will only have access to
and use the data they need to perform their functions.  The relevant suppliers are often IT
suppliers (who, for example, host or support our IT systems, including
information about you such as Identifiers and the information described in
the “Cookies and automated technologies” section below), premises management
companies (who, for example, look after physical security at our
buildings, and therefore need to know about you to allow access to our
buildings) and/or back office finance and accounting management providers
(who, for example, need to handle details, such as Identifiers,
professional or employment-related information, and financial information
like a  bank account number of
persons in order to process accounts payable and receivable). We also
engage suppliers who provide technology services and solutions who, for
example, provide video interview and skills assessment tools and may need
access to your Identifiers, Education and Qualifications, Correspondence
and Feedback, and Social Media Information.
To other
members of The Adecco Group. We
are part of “The
Adecco Group”, an organization of related companies located across the
world whom are all subsidiaries of the same ultimate parent company,
Adecco Group AG (a legal entity based in Switzerland).
The Adecco Group companies perform a range of services including but
not limited to temporary staffing and direct hire placement services,
payroll services, recruitment and selection services, testing solutions
services, career transition services, talent development services,
training and education services, outplacement and international mobility
services.  We may share
your information with other members of The Adecco Group for different
reasons:
information is shared with members of The Adecco
Group that provide IT functions for the The Adecco Group companies
world-wide;
information may be shared with other affiliate
companies of The Adecco Group locally and/or globally in furtherance of
the services we or The Adecco Group provides.  A list of the countries in which we
operate is available in the ‘choose your country’ function of our website
at www.adeccogroup.com.
Government
& law enforcement. We will share your data with government, regulators
or law enforcement agencies if, at our sole discretion, we consider that
we are legally obliged or authorized to do so or we believe it would be
prudent to do so; and/or
Corporate
reorganization. As part of due diligence relating to (or
implementation of) a merger, acquisition or other business transaction, we
may need to disclose your data to the prospective seller or buyer and
their advisers.
We do not sell your Personal Information to third parties.
Back to top
Cookies and automated technology
Automatic Data Collection. In addition to collecting Personal Information, we may use automatic data collection technologies to collect certain statistical (non-identifiable) information about your equipment, browsing actions, and patterns. This includes (i) details about your visits to our Website, which may include traffic data and location data, date and time of access, frequency and other communication data; and (ii) information about your computer and internet connection, which may include your IP address, operating system, browser type, and host domain; and (iii) details of referring website actions and patterns.
Cookies. We may collect information from you using a “cookie.” “Cookies” are small bits of data cached or stored on your computer based on your internet activity. They can be placed on your computer both by us as well as by third parties with whom we have a relationship, such as web analytic services and advertising networks. Cookies help us track and understand how individuals use and interact with our Website. For more information on the types of cookies that we use and your ability to disable cookies, please see the “Your choices regarding your Personal Information” section below and our Cookie Policy available at https://www.ajilon.com/cookie-policy/.
Web Beacons. We use a technology known as web beacons to collect your web log information. A web beacon is a small graphic used on a website or within an e-mail message designed to track pages viewed or messages opened. Web log information is gathered by the computer that hosts our Website (called a "webserver”) when you visit our Website. Web beacons in e-mails help us determine which of our e-mail messages were opened and whether a message was acted upon. They also help us analyze the effectiveness of our web pages by measuring the number of visitors to certain pages of our Website and how many visitors click on key elements of it.
Social Media Plug-ins. Our Website uses social media plugins (“Plugins”) from the social networks such as Facebook, LinkedIn, Twitter, and Instagram to enable you to easily share information with others. We may use information collected from the Plugins to learn about your interests and to help us better understand how to serve you. This information may include your preferences about how to contact you or further develop a business or professional relationship with you as well as demographic data.  For more information, please visit our Cookie Policy at https://www.ajilon.com/cookie-policy/.
Back to top
International Users
This General Privacy Policy is intended for individuals located in North America. Users who use the Website understand that their data will be collected, used, and stored in North America, in addition to other countries in the world (for example, in other countries from which IT functions are provided to us).
Back to top
Do we transfer or store your data outside the United States?
Your Personal Information may be transferred to and/or stored in any country where we conduct business, which includes outside North America. By using our Website or by otherwise providing information to us, you understand that the information from or about you or your use of our Website may be transferred to and/or stored in countries outside of your country of residence, including the United States.
Back to top
Data Security
We maintain commercially reasonable security safeguards designed to protect the Personal Information we collect against unauthorized use, disclosure, alteration or destruction. Although we aim to protect the security and integrity of the Personal Information we collect, we cannot guarantee or warrant that any information, during transmission through the Internet or while stored on our system or otherwise in any case, is 100% secure from intrusion by others. If you have reason to believe that your interaction with us is not secure or that data has been compromised, please immediately notify us of the problem by contacting us using the contact information below.
Back to top
Your choices regarding your Personal Information
Disabling Cookies and Managing the Collection of Your Personal Information. At any time, you can disable cookies by adjusting your browser settings. Each browser is different, so please refer to the specific instructions related to your browser to learn more about cookie-related and other privacy and security settings that may be available to you.
Please note, by disabling cookies, you may not be able to take full advantage of the services offered by our Website.  For more information, please visit our Cookie Policy at https://www.ajilon.com/cookie-policy/.
Do Not Track. Currently we do not alter our information collection and use practices in response to Do Not Track signals.
Commercial E-mails, Newsletters, and Other Communications.  Where we send marketing or other communications to you, you may opt out of receiving any further communications by contacting us or using the ‘unsubscribe’ or ‘opt-out’ function when available. You can also exercise your opt-out right at any time by contacting us using the information listed in the ”Contact” section below and providing the following information: your name, your email address, a contact telephone number, the marketing communications you would like to opt out of receiving.
Back to top
Your rights
You have certain legal rights with respect to the Personal Information that you provide and/or which we obtain about you depending on the state/country where you reside.  For example, if you are a resident of California, the California Consumer Privacy Act (“CCPA”) (Civil Code § 1798.100, et seq.) provides you with specific rights regarding your Personal Information depending on the nature of your relationship with us.
Where applicable, your rights include, among others:
Right to be informed about collection, sale or disclosure:  You have the right to be informed of the categories of Personal Information that we collect about you as well as the categories of sources from which the Personal Information was collected. You also have the right to be informed of the business or commercial purposes for which we use, disclose, or sell, your Personal Information as well as the categories of third parties with whom we share that Personal Information, as set forth in this General Privacy Policy.
Right to access and obtain a copy of your Personal Information:  You have the right to request that we disclose certain information to you about our collection, use, and disclosure of your Personal Information over the past 12 months. Once we have verified your identity, we will disclose the specific pieces of Personal Information we collected about you in a portable and, to the extent technically feasible, in a readily useable format.
Right to delete:  In certain circumstances, you may have the right to request that your Personal Information is deleted, subject to certain exceptions.
Right to opt-out of the sale of Personal Information:  We do not sell your information.  However, certain laws afford you the right to opt out of the sale of your Personal Information.
Right to equal service for exercising your privacy rights:  Unless permitted by applicable law, we will not discriminate against you when you exercise your privacy rights under the California Consumer Privacy Act or other applicable law, including by: denying you goods or services; charging you different prices or rates for goods or services, including through the use of discounts or other benefits or by imposing penalties; providing you with a different level of quality of good or services; or suggesting that you will receive a different price or rate for goods or services or a different level of quality of goods or services.
To exercise your rights, please use the contact information listed in the “Contact” section below.
Candidates may access, review, correct or update their Personal Information in accordance with our Candidate Privacy Information Statement available at https://www.ajilon.com/candidate-policy/.
Verifying Your Identity
To exercise the rights described above, it may be necessary for us to verify your identity or authority to make the request and confirm the Personal Information relates to you. To exercise your rights, we will collect your name, e-mail and/or telephone to verify your identity. Upon receiving your request, we may also contact you via e-mail and/or other secured communication channel to verify your identity by asking you additional security questions in order to match your identity with the data we maintain about you.
For residents of California only, you, or a person registered with the California Secretary of State that you authorize to act on your behalf, may make a verifiable consumer request related to your Personal Information.  Your authorized representative may be required to submit a declaration or affidavit demonstrating that they have the authority to act on your behalf.
Once we have verified your identity, we will disclose the specific pieces of Personal Information we collected about you, by mail or electronically, at your option, in a readily usable format that allows you to transmit the information from one entity to another entity without hindrance.
Please note that if we cannot verify your identity, we are not obligated to provide you or your authorized representative information regarding your Personal Information.
To submit a request or for more information on how to submit a request, please contact us using the information listed in the “Contact” section below. Making a verifiable consumer request does not require you to create an account with us.
Back to top
Shine the Light
California’s “Shine the Light” law (Civil Code Code § 1798.83) permits users of our Website that are California residents to request certain information regarding our disclosure of Personal Information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please contact us using the information listed in the “Contact” section below.
Back to top
Children’s privacy
Our Website is designed and intended for adults. By accessing and/or using our Website, you represent that you are a legal adult.  If you are not a legal adult, you must have your parent or legal guardian access and use the Website for you. If you want to purchase any goods or services that may be offered on our Website, such purchase(s) must be made by your parent or legal guardian on your behalf.
Our Website is not intended for, and we do not knowingly collect information from or otherwise market our website or other materials to children under thirteen (13) years of age. If you are a parent or guardian of a child under the age of thirteen (13) and believe that he or she has disclosed Personal Information to us, please contact us using the information listed in the “Contact” section below. You may review and request the deletion of your child’s Personal Information or prohibit the further use of such information.
Back to top
Changes to this General Privacy Policy
The terms of this General Privacy Policy may change from time to time. We shall publish any material changes to this General Privacy Policy through appropriate notices either on this Website or contacting you using other communication channels. The date this General Privacy Policy was last revised is identified at the top of the page in the “Last Updated” legend.
Back to top
Contact
rights with respect to your Personal Information (as applicable), please contact us by email at  privacy@ajilon.com, by telephone at 800.793.7657 option 6, or by visiting our privacy rights request webform at https://adeccogroup.force.com/privacy/s/?bu=Ajilon.
Back to top
